(Sheldon:)I sense judgment on your part.
(Leonard:)No, no.
(Leonard:)Maybe a little.
(Sheldon:)May I suggest that your
criticism is based on jealousy.
(Leonard:)Jealousy? What do I
have to be jealous of?
(Sheldon:)I have a functioning
and satisfying relationship
(Sheldon:)with a female.
(Sheldon:)You have none.
(Leonard:)Oh, right. That.
(Sheldon:)Jealousy is an ugly
green-eyed monster--
(Sheldon:)not unlike the Hulk--
(Sheldon:)who, by the way,
also has a girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)In this iteration,
Jennifer Connelly,
(Sheldon:)whom you may recall as
the girlfriend of Russell Crowe
in A Beautiful Mind,
(Sheldon:)a feel-good romp if
there ever was one.
(Leonard:)I'm not jealous.
(Sheldon:)Leonard not jealous.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪